// //credits:https://www.funtrivia.com/en/Television/Breaking-Bad-20207_5.html
// //Questions script
// //creating array with number, questions, and answers


// let score = 0;
 
// for( let i =0; i < questions.length; i++) {
//     let response = window.prompt(questions[i].prompt);
//     if (response == questions[i].correctAnswer) {
//         score++;
//         alert("correct")
//     } else {
//         alert("Wrong")
//     }

// } 


// let scoreE = document.querySelector('.scorePoints')
// let answerC = document.querySelector('.answerChoices')
// answerC.addEventListener('click', (correctAnswer)=> {
//     score += 10

//     if (score < 110) {
//         scoreE.innerText = score
//     } else {
//         declareWinner()
//     }
// })


// let questions = [
//     //index 0
//     {   ques: 1,
//         prompt: "Walter White's transformation from nerdy high school chemistry teacher to criminal kingpin all started with what specific medical diagnosis?",
//         correctAnswer: "Lung Cancer",
//         answers: [
//             "Lung Cancer",
//             "Rabies",
//             "Covid-19",
//             "AIDs"
//         ] 
//     },
//     //index 1
//     {   ques: 2,
//         prompt: "Hank, Walt's brother-in-law, is a DEA agent. What does DEA stand for?",
//         correctAnswer: "Drug Enforcement Administration",
//         answers: [
//             "Dog Enforcement Admin",
//             "Drug Empire Animal",
//             "Drug Enforcement Administration",
//             "Drug Enforcement Agency"
//         ]
//     },
//     //index 2
//     {   ques: 3,
//         prompt: "Walter White led a pretty normal life in the south-western part of the United States. All this changed after receiving a diagnoses. Which state does the show take place in?",
//         correctAnswer: "New Mexico",
//         answers: [
//             "Texas",
//             "New Mexico",
//             "Arizona",
//             "Utah"
//         ]
//     },
//     //index 3
//     {   ques: 4,
//         prompt: "Walter White is the main character in the show. What is the name of the actor who portrays him?",
//         correctAnswer: "Bryan Cranston",
//         answers: [
//             "Michael B. Jordon",
//             "Irving Johnson",
//             "Bryan Kraft",
//             "Bryan Cranston"
//         ]
//     },
//     //index 4
//     {   ques: 5,
//         prompt: "What country is Gus from originally?",
//         correctAnswer: "Chile",
//         answers: [
//             "Chile",
//             "Mexico",
//             "Brazil",
//             "Spain"
//         ]
//     },
//     //index 5
//     {   ques: 6,
//         prompt: "Who is Walters attorney?",
//         correctAnswer: "Saul Goodman",
//         answers: [
//             "Tuco",
//             "Jesse Pinkman",
//             "Saul Ramirez",
//             "Saul Goodman"
//         ]
//     },
//     //index 6
//     {   ques: 7,
//         prompt: "What nickname does Walt use in the show?",
//         correctAnswer: "Heisenberg",
//         answers: [
//             "Henry",
//             "Iceberg",
//             "Heisenberg",
//             "Walter Berg"
//         ]
//     },
//     //index 7
//     {   ques: 8,
//         prompt: "Who was Gus' partner in Los Pollos Hermanos and was killed by Hector tio Salamanca??",
//         correctAnswer: "Max",
//         answers: [
//             "Max",
//             "Tuco",
//             "Hector jr",
//             "Jesse Pinkman"
//         ]
//     },
//     //index 8
//     {   ques: 9,
//         prompt: "Hank, Walt's brother-in-law, is a DEA agent. What does DEA stand for?",
//         correctAnswer: "Drug Enforcement Administration",
//         answers: [
//             "Dog Enforcement Admin",
//             "Drug Empire Animal",
//             "Drug Enforcement Administration",
//             "Drug Enforcement Agency"
//         ]
//     },
//     //index 9
//     {   ques:  10,
//         prompt: "In what year was Walt awarded an award for his contributing research that led to a Nobel Prize?",
//         correctAnswer: 1985,
//         answers: [
//             1985,
//             1999,
//             2001,
//             2004
//         ]
//     }
// ]












